MUHAMMAD NAUFAL FADLLUR ROHMAN

 $\underline{fadllur.naufal@gmail.com} \mid +62\ 822\ 1880\ 3756 \mid \underline{linkedin.com/in/naufalfadllur/} \mid \underline{github.com/fadllurnaufal/} \mid \underline{naufalfadllur.vercel.app}$

Bandung, Indonesia

I am a 2023 graduate from Widyatama University, Bachelor's degree in Informatics Engineering. I have experience in organizational activities, internships, and freelance work. These experiences have helped me refine my softskill and programming skills, allowing me to design and implement several applications that incorporate innovation, the latest technology, and creative problems solving. I see every opportunity as a chance to continue learning and growing in the field of information technology.

EXPERIENCE

SMK Negeri 6 Bandung - Bandung, Indonesia

Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

Web Developer

Task

- · Designing, developing, and implementing a guidance counseling system and a correspondence management system.
- Developing the backend business logic for all applications to ensure optimal performance and security.
- Collaborating with the development team to ensure seamless integration between application components and consistent functionality.

Daarut Tauhiid Akademi - Bandung, Indonesia

Dec 2022 - Oct 2023

Web Developer

Task

- Developing new features in the application for monitoring students.
- · Designing and implementing monthly report features for student monitoring.
- Managing the database for storing student data, ensuring data integrity and security.
- Identifying and resolving technical issues that arise during application development and operation.

Kumaw Eyelash - Bandung, Indonesia

Sep 2023 - Oct 2023

Web Developer

Task

- Designing and developing a landing page and a booking form for customers.
- Managing the database for storing customers data, ensuring data integrity and security.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree

Informatics Engineering, Widyatama University

Sep 2019 - Aug 2023

Grade : 3.61/ 4.00

ORGANIZATION

HIMATIF Jan 2022 - Apr 2023

Head of Interest and Talent Division

- Leading my peers in all activities.
- Guiding them in performing tasks.
- Making decisions in all aspects.

OTHER

- Technologies: HTML/CSS/PHP/Javascript/Laravel/ReactJs/Git/MySQL
- Software Design: Figma/Framer
- Soft Skills: Responsibility Adaptable Good Teamwork
- Languages: Indonesia (Native), English (Proficient)